utopia the good place a good place for
here and now and for everywhere and
forever multi-levels utopia the inner
utopia and the outer utopia the inner
utopia cultivating the inner garden
within the inner temple and the in the
citadel the outer utopia cultivating the
outer garden or from the outer temple in
the outer citadel nutopia the playground
where anyone can find a game that they
want to play where no one is forced into
a game if they do not want to play they
can find the game which develops their
agency and their sovereignty utopia is
the playground which includes everybody
and excludes no one it embraces all
potential utopia forever utopia has the
infinite playground where all equipment
all constructs all possibilities are
available to you utopia forever means
utopia forever changing because utopia
whatever the same is stagnation so
utopia is a is an idea it's a it's a
it's a it's a it's a meta it's a meta
playground but it's it's it's an
abstraction it's not a place it's a it's
a way of being in the playground it's a
way of playing with others the meta
playground which generates playgrounds
utopia has the tapas of the place which
produces other Tokai other places
utopia not as only indeterminate
something customisable by anyone set of
principles can be applied to one's
individual and collective needs the
individual utopia and the collective
utopia under need for both need of the
chamber of solitude the room of one's
own but also the need of the Commons of
one's own to one that one belongs a
community at communal space though one
can be together happily where games are
provided games organized one doesn't
have to think how one needs to play but
then complain richness leading free
utopium playground is a place where
everybody belongs or at least everybody
can find a place in which they belong
longing feels like there's something in
that that's important longing is is an
embodied sense of being part of
something which isn't just you like an
important part of a fabric of which you
are a thread something like that and
that without your thread or if your
threads the wrong color if you don't
show up as the right kind of thread the
whole fabric is not quite right to
belong to be longed to be somewhere for
a long time will be somewhere long
enough that one starts to plant roots
into the ground the ones thread becomes
woven into the total tapestry a place of
one's
the place that belongs to oneself one's
own cord corner of the garden a place
where well one will not be uprooted
where one will not be able to be long
one will only be able to be short being
transplanted against one will know you
cannot be here now you must move you
cannot stay at your home you must go to
your work go to where you have to give
your energy by another person in this
place that's really beautiful be long be
in the place for a long time put down
roots build relationships build networks
that's a really beautiful way to look at
it the the notions of commitment and
responsibility come to mind that these
are inextricably part of this utopia
right it's not just head an ism and sex
and drugs and whatever the you want
whenever the you want it they the
belonging requires you as Jordan
Peterson would say not just to play this
game will win this game but to be the
kind of person who gets advice to play
games over and over and over again to
join in with other people's games to
join in with the collective game
collectively designing the collective
game where everybody wants to return to
play to plant a totem in one's home that
one will respect for the length of one's
life the one will return who would turn
to sacrifice you to give oneself over
and over again the spin around the totem
to spin the trunk around the photon
and for everybody to dance around that
axis mundi letting loose their anima
letting loose the anima Mundi joining
together in two acts SEMA into the
synergy of the pole and the polarities
generating the field of the good place
synergy and relationship dancing around
the totem pole creating a sympathetic
vibration between all of the
participants that once created washes
over and reinforces and binds the other
what is it the force passes through us
and binds the universe together
something something like that that kind
of image the ability to leave and return
that you you've still been there a long
time you have the right to leave go off
explore try new games come back again
their experience in those games enriches
this game because you are a trusted
member of this utopia a center of one's
world one can return to an attachment to
that Center like a child is attached to
the parent knows that you go and explore
and it returned through its core and
there everything will be safe no matter
what suffering is experienced by
whatever accident out there and the big
unknown safe that one would be glad for
one school
the exploration of the unknown the
pushing back the pushing back the
boundaries of what it means to be in the
world the resilience of the utopia to
create games that our debt to the New
Territories which are being exposed the
meta principles of the utopia being
maintained the richness of the
interweaving of the fabric only getting
richer as those threads have more thread
each of those threads have more threads
that make them up enriching the overall
tapestry at a fractal level the eternal
utopia